一旦forecast adapter能够正常工作，我们就要修改forecast adapter
Once a forecast adapter works, we want to modify it so
使它能返回为today列表项返回另一种view类型。
that it can return a second item view type for the
通常在子类中，getViewTypeCount方法会返回1种类型
today list item. Normally in the sub class, getViewTypeCount return to
但是我们会重写这个方法，使它为两种不同的布局而返回2。
one, but we're going to override it so it returns two for
但是它怎么知道什么时候
the two different layouts. But how does it know when to
返回什么类型呢？ 所以，我们要重写getItemViewType方法的时候
use one there or the other? Well, we override getItemViewType so
如果当前位置处于0，
that when the position in the list is zero, then we
那么我们就认为它是TODAY类型的。反之，就是FUTURE_DAY类型的
say that it's the TODAY view type. Otherwise, it's the FUTURE_DAY
这两种类型在之前就已经声明了。
view type. These two view types are declared up
它们只是通过整形数值来代表View的类型。
above. These are just integer representations of the view type.
返回值范围必须从0开始
The numbering has to start at zero because these values
因为位置的数值必须小于getViewTypeCount的返回值
can not be greater than or equal to getViewTypeCount. So,
所以这里合法的返回值只有0和1
the possible values for us are zero and one,
继而可知0对应view_type_today
so that we know that zero always maps to the
而1对应view_type_future_day
view_type_today and that one always maps to view_type_future_day. We're going to
我们会在newView方法里用到这组对应关系
use this information in the new View method. Remember that
还记得吗，我们之前已经加载了list_item_forecast.xml。
previously we inflated the list_item_forecast.xml. Now, we're going to use
那么现在就是用getItemViewType方法来确定该用哪个布局
the getItemViewType to determine whether we should use one
在“to do”中来实现这个操作。
layout or the other. Fill in the to do
LayoutId指资源ID，
to address this behavior. LayoutId refers to resource ID,
它的表现形式是R.layout.某项资源
which is in the form of r.layout.something. We don't
我们无需重构bindView方法
have to reform the bindView method because it will
它自己会进行绑定操作。因为today布局中该资源的ID和future布局中
continue to work. That's because the IDs are the
该资源的ID是一样的。
same between the today layout and the future day layout.
当你完成后，你的程序就会是这个样子滴。
This is what your app should look like when you're
today的布局和其它日子的布局是不同的。
done. The today layout is different from the rest of the
自己动手试试看！把上面这些修改添加到你的程序里，
days. Go ahead and make these changes in your app and
并完成To Do里的工作。 完成后在方格里打钩。
then finish the To Do. Check this box when you're done.